knowreviewtip.com 2015-12-07

# Know Review Tip | Privacy Policy & Disclaimer

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which knowreviewtip.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.knowreviewtip.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Iknowc.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Know Review Tips may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service  
    Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To personalize user experience  
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
    We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. **We never sell or share your email address / Personal information with anyone, we respect your Privacy.**  

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies , NOT OURS.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Changes to this privacy policy

Iknowc has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us using [contact form](http://www.knowreviewtip.com/contact-us/).

## Disclaimer

Disclaimer   
knowreviewtip is a site that provides gadgets review , products demo , information on technology , diy , geek and much more .  The main motive of knowreviewtip.com is to deliver the latest information  from tech world to its viewers & to delivery free knowledge . 

No guarantee – We always try our best to make sure that information on our site is correct but knowreviewtip.com does not grantee whether the information is accurate or not , so kindly search on other sources for the same query.  
knowreviewtip.com will never  accept any responsibility for any financial consequences that may arise from the information provided herein .

Posting Comments   
Users can post comments inorder to share there views . Please note that always use valid email address & user name while posting comment on site , in case e-mail address found to be  invalid then  comment will be marked as  SPAM . ALSO you agree that you are fully aware of what you are posting as  comment & you  agree that you are  posting  non copyrighted material / comment  . When ever you post comment , your IP address is recorded for the safeguarding. We never sell or share your email address with anyone, we respect your Privacy. 

You are  full responsible for the contents of your comment that you are posting and no one rather than  you will be held liable in case of any inquiries or prosecution by any government authorities .

E-MAIL Subscription  
E-mail subscription on Know Review Tips is powered by Google Feed Burner , therefore knowreviewtip.com must not be responsible for any problem or any losses that might have occurred while using  E-mail subscription . knowreviewtip.com doesn’t send spam email , but in case you want to unsubscribe then you can just click on the link for unsubscribing  which can be found on the email that users get .  
NOTE: This Disclaimer is subject to change at anytime without any notification & changes made will be effective immediately .

### WaterMark on Images

Watermark on images is just a Digital prove that the image is uploaded on or downloaded from knowreviewtip. Images or any other logo are trademarks of there respected owners.

 _ **THANKS & BEST REGARDS **_
